Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) Records UA032
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student records, 1918 -- 2012; 1918 -- 2009; UA032.002; 38.9 Linear Feet
  - Dennison, Frances (Mrs. E. Allen, Jr.), 1941-42, 1941 -- 1942; UA032.002.105.00054 (Box 105)
  - Cox, Deona F. (Webber), Mrs. Ralph W., 1951; UA032.002.105.00055 (Box 105)
  - O'Keefe, Mary E., 1951; UA032.002.105.00056 (Box 105)
  - McCann, Marie Loretta, 1952; UA032.002.105.00057 (Box 105)
  - Levenson, Mrs. Moses, 1955; UA032.002.105.00058 (Box 105)
  - Savage, Bettina I., n.d., UA032.002.105.00059 (Box 105)
  - French, Ruth Allerton, 1957; UA032.002.105.00060 (Box 105)
  - Abbott, Marc W., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.112.00001 (Box 112)
  - Abeles, Janet, 1974 -- 1976; UA032.002.112.00002 (Box 112)
  - Ablard, Katie, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.112.00003 (Box 112)
  - Abrams, Elizabeth Joan, 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.112.00004 (Box 112)
  - Abrams, Maida, 1960 -- 1962; UA032.002.112.00005 (Box 112)
  - Abrams, Peggy Lynn, 1970 -- 1974; UA032.002.112.00006 (Box 112)
  - Abrams, Stephanie, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.112.00007 (Box 112)
  - Accardi, Michael, 1979 -- 1981; UA032.002.112.00008 (Box 112)
  - Adams, Charletta, 1973 -- 1974; UA032.002.112.00009 (Box 112)
  - Adcock, Elizabeth, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.112.00010 (Box 112)
  - Agar, Nancy Helen, 1976 -- 1978; UA032.002.112.00011 (Box 112)
  - Alakie (Litwin), Robin W., 1994 -- 1997; UA032.002.112.00012 (Box 112)
  - Albrecht-Carrie, Kirsten, 1965 -- 1970; UA032.002.112.00013 (Box 112)
  - Albright, Patricia Gale, 1968 -- 1979; UA032.002.112.00014 (Box 112)
  - Alden, Margaret, 1993; UA032.002.112.00015 (Box 112)
  - Alessio, Mary Brunn, 1979 -- 1981; UA032.002.112.00016 (Box 112)
  - Alexander, Kris E., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.112.00017 (Box 112)
  - Alfredsson, Valerie, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.112.00018 (Box 112)
  - Alguire, Catherine Ann, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.112.00019 (Box 112)
  - Allard, Mary Lou, 1966 -- 1969; UA032.002.112.00020 (Box 112)
  - Allen, Diane Hinman, 1937 -- 1960; UA032.002.112.00021 (Box 112)
  - Allen, Susan Bishop, 1973 -- 1974; UA032.002.112.00022 (Box 112)
  - Al-Shahristani, Zahra, 2004; UA032.002.112.00023 (Box 112)
  - Altermann, Jamie, 2001 -- 2004; UA032.002.112.00024 (Box 112)
  - Altman, Laurie Beth, 1975 -- 1976; UA032.002.112.00025 (Box 112)
  - Altman, Stephanie P., 1986 -- 1990; UA032.002.112.00026 (Box 112)
  - Amara, Debora Ann, 1981 -- 1984; UA032.002.112.00027 (Box 112)
  - Ambrosino, Carmen, 1995 -- 1998; UA032.002.112.00028 (Box 112)
  - Ames, Heather R., 2004 -- 2008; UA032.002.112.00029 (Box 112)
  - Amin, Kimberly, 1993 -- 2000; UA032.002.112.00030 (Box 112)
  - Anderson, Gail Agnes, 1965 -- 1967; UA032.002.112.00031 (Box 112)
  - Anderson, Lisa V., 1999 -- 2003; UA032.002.112.00032 (Box 112)
  - Anderson, Mercedes, 2000 -- 2003; UA032.002.112.00033 (Box 112)
  - Anderson, Ruth A., 1980 -- 1981; UA032.002.112.00034 (Box 112)
  - Andersson, Priscilla, R., 1965 -- 1967; UA032.002.112.00035 (Box 112)
  - Andres, Nancy H., 1960 -- 1964; UA032.002.112.00036 (Box 112)
  - Andreski, Stephen, 1993 -- 1996; UA032.002.112.00037 (Box 112)
  - Andrews, Linda L., 1981 -- 1982; UA032.002.112.00038 (Box 112)
  - Angeles, Valerie, 1969 -- 1973; UA032.002.112.00039 (Box 112)
  - Antouson, Joyce, 1966 -- 1972; UA032.002.112.00040 (Box 112)
  - Apfel, Eileen Ruth, 1975 -- 1976; UA032.002.112.00041 (Box 112)
  - Appleton, Elizabeth J., 1977 -- 1980; UA032.002.112.00042 (Box 112)
  - Aranda, Roslyn M., 1982 -- 1987; UA032.002.112.00043 (Box 112)
  - Arias, Maria E., 1984 -- 1988; UA032.002.112.00044 (Box 112)
  - Arluk, Julie, 1992 -- 2002; UA032.002.112.00045 (Box 112)
  - Armstrong, Ellis, 1973 -- 1974; UA032.002.112.00046 (Box 112)
  - Arndt, Emily, 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.112.00047 (Box 112)
  - Arnold, Allison, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.112.00048 (Box 112)
  - Arnold, Betsy, 1957 -- 1960; UA032.002.112.00049 (Box 112)
  - Arnold, Katherine, 1973 -- 1975; UA032.002.112.00050 (Box 112)
  - Basseches, Thomas J., 1988 -- 1991; UA032.002.113.00001 (Box 113)
  - Loftus, Sue Anne (Basu), 1955 -- 1960; UA032.002.113.00002 (Box 113)
  - Batich, Leonora, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.113.00003 (Box 113)
  - Baum, Barbara, 1970 -- 1974; UA032.002.113.00004 (Box 113)
  - Lubov, Nancy Ann (Baum), 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.113.00005 (Box 113)
  - Bavaro, Stephanie M, 1988; UA032.002.113.00006 (Box 113)
  - Baxter, B. Scott, 1993 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00007 (Box 113)
  - Baxter, Diana Hemenway, 1978; UA032.002.113.00008 (Box 113)
  - Beaton, Meredith J., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.113.00009 (Box 113)
  - Beaucamp, June A., 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.113.00010 (Box 113)
  - Becker, Marjory Ann, 1973 -- 1974; UA032.002.113.00011 (Box 113)
  - Becker, Wendy Joan, 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.113.00012 (Box 113)
  - Bedell, Gary, 1979 -- 1982; UA032.002.113.00013 (Box 113)
  - Bedi, Hitaoshi, 2005 -- 2006; UA032.002.113.00014 (Box 113)
  - Bedrick, Amy, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00015 (Box 113)
  - Beekmann, Virginia, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00016 (Box 113)
  - Bell, Phillipa J., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.113.00017 (Box 113)
  - Bellavance, Diane Marie, 1964 -- 1968; UA032.002.113.00018 (Box 113)
  - Belle, Kunegunda, Irene, 1964 -- 1969; UA032.002.113.00019 (Box 113)
  - Belostock, Elisa, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.113.00020 (Box 113)
  - Beltz, Linda, 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.113.00021 (Box 113)
  - Berg, Doree S., 1970 -- 1973; UA032.002.113.00022 (Box 113)
  - Berg, Marjorie Lee, 1964 -- 1967; UA032.002.113.00023 (Box 113)
  - Berger, Ellen, 1974 -- 1976; UA032.002.113.00024 (Box 113)
  - Berger, Susan E., 1977 -- 1983; UA032.002.113.00025 (Box 113)
  - Lindsay, Margaret E. (Bergerou), 1961 -- 1964; UA032.002.113.00026 (Box 113)
  - Bergmann, Leslie B., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.113.00027 (Box 113)
  - Bergquist, Jonathan, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.113.00028 (Box 113)
  - Berk, Stephanie L., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.113.00029 (Box 113)
  - Berkofsky, Margaret, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.113.00030 (Box 113)
  - Berman, Cynthia Ruth, 1966 -- 1970; UA032.002.113.00031 (Box 113)
  - Bernardin, Miriam D., 1978 -- 1982; UA032.002.113.00032 (Box 113)
  - Bernsteub, Alan Jr., 1983 -- 1989; UA032.002.113.00033 (Box 113)
  - Bernstein, Marybeth, 1991 -- 1994; UA032.002.113.00034 (Box 113)
  - Bernstein, Olga, 2003 -- 2006; UA032.002.113.00035 (Box 113)
  - Berry, Bridget, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.113.00036 (Box 113)
  - Berry, Jennifer E., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.113.00037 (Box 113)
  - Bertolaccini, Amy C., 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.113.00038 (Box 113)
  - Ferzoco (Bertrand), Esther, 1988 -- 1992; UA032.002.113.00039 (Box 113)
  - Besen, Merri Beth, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.113.00040 (Box 113)
  - Bestmann, Shelley, 1971 -- 1974; UA032.002.113.00041 (Box 113)
  - Bethel, Debra Ann, 2000 -- 2003; UA032.002.113.00042 (Box 113)
  - Woelky, Joan (Beyman), 1960 -- 1962; UA032.002.113.00043 (Box 113)
  - Martin, Susan E. (Biagini), 1970 -- 1972; UA032.002.113.00044 (Box 113)
  - Bibbo, Mellisa J, 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.113.00045 (Box 113)
  - Bibeault, Anne, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.113.00046 (Box 113)
  - Bicknell, Leah, 2005; UA032.002.113.00047 (Box 113)
  - Biederman, Patricia Ann, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.113.00048 (Box 113)
  - Biggs, Barbara Ann, 1956 -- 1961; UA032.002.113.00049 (Box 113)
  - Jocobson, Elaine Joan (Bikofasky), 1955 -- 1960; UA032.002.113.00050 (Box 113)
  - Bilton, Wilam, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.113.00051 (Box 113)
  - Bixon, Lolita, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.113.00052 (Box 113)
  - Blackburn, Dorothy J. (Colby), 1963 -- 1964; UA032.002.113.00053 (Box 113)
  - Blagbrough, Jean, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.113.00054 (Box 113)
  - Blais, Rebecca, 2003 -- 2005; UA032.002.113.00055 (Box 113)
  - Blaisdell, Jodi, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.113.00056 (Box 113)
  - Blake, Amy Kathleen, 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.113.00057 (Box 113)
  - Blake, Colleen S., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.113.00058 (Box 113)
  - Blandini, Joseph, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.113.00059 (Box 113)
  - Blatz, Mary Catherine, 1985 -- 1987; UA032.002.113.00060 (Box 113)
  - Blaylock, Catherine C., 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.113.00061 (Box 113)
  - Blemker, Heidi, UA032.002.113.00062 (Box 113)
  - Hassenfeld, Ellen (Block), 1962 -- 1964; UA032.002.113.00063 (Box 113)
  - Blodgett, Stephanie L., 1998 -- 2001; UA032.002.113.00064 (Box 113)
  - Blond, Laurel, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.113.00065 (Box 113)
  - Bloom, Gail Miriam, 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.113.00066 (Box 113)
  - Roesch, Stephanie Dale (Bloom), 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.113.00067 (Box 113)
  - Blue, David, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00068 (Box 113)
  - Blumenthal, Jill Ruth, 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.113.00069 (Box 113)
  - Blumenthal, Susan Jane, 1978 -- 1982; UA032.002.113.00070 (Box 113)
  - Bobb-Semple, Yonnette E., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.113.00071 (Box 113)
  - Bogdan, Karen, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.113.00072 (Box 113)
  - Bogost, Erin, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.113.00073 (Box 113)
  - Feinbaum, Katherine Majorie (Bohem), 1966 -- 1970; UA032.002.113.00074 (Box 113)
  - Boiselle, Pauline Anne, 1985 -- 1990; UA032.002.113.00075 (Box 113)
  - Bolanos-Hernandez, Lizette, 1999 -- 2002; UA032.002.113.00076 (Box 113)
  - Bolanos-Hernandez, Lizette, 1981 -- 1990; UA032.002.113.00077 (Box 113)
  - Bolles, Clara, 1977 -- 1982; UA032.002.113.00078 (Box 113)
  - Bombara, Maire A, 1983 -- 1987; UA032.002.113.00079 (Box 113)
  - Bond, Kimberly, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00080 (Box 113)
  - Bond, Mary Elizabeth, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.113.00081 (Box 113)
  - Bonenfant, Denise Renee, 1967 -- 1971; UA032.002.113.00082 (Box 113)
  - Boorstein, Vida, 1964 -- 1966; UA032.002.113.00083 (Box 113)
  - Bornstein, Jodi, 2003 -- 2004; UA032.002.113.00084 (Box 113)
  - Bortner, Eileen Carol, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.113.00085 (Box 113)
  - Bosco, Diane Marie, 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.113.00086 (Box 113)
  - Conover, Virginia Andrews (Bouchard), 1965 -- 1969; UA032.002.113.00087 (Box 113)
  - Boucher, Joseph, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.113.00088 (Box 113)
  - Boucher, Linda, 1978 -- 1982; UA032.002.113.00089 (Box 113)
  - Boucher, Mary F., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.113.00090 (Box 113)
  - Boudreau, Cynthia A., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.113.00091 (Box 113)
  - Boudreau, Jean Marie, 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.113.00092 (Box 113)
  - Boulias, Jamie, 2004 -- 2007; UA032.002.113.00093 (Box 113)
  - Bourgoin, Rebecca L., 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.113.00094 (Box 113)
  - Bove, Laurie A, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.113.00095 (Box 113)
  - Boyce, Eileen Marie (Paulson), 1967 -- 1971; UA032.002.113.00096 (Box 113)
  - Boyce, Lisa, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.113.00097 (Box 113)
  - Boynton, Sarah, 1989 -- 1994; UA032.002.113.00098 (Box 113)
  - Bracken, Stacey, 1999; UA032.002.113.00099 (Box 113)
  - Sand, Sonja L. (Bradburn), 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.113.00100 (Box 113)
  - Bradlee, Lisa, 1989 -- 1992; UA032.002.113.00101 (Box 113)
  - Bradshaw, Hilary, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.113.00102 (Box 113)
  - Brady, Helen, 2002 -- 2003; UA032.002.113.00103 (Box 113)
  - Brady, Jonathan T., 2000 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00001 (Box 114)
  - Brandt, Robin L., 1980 -- 1982; UA032.002.114.00002 (Box 114)
  - Brasic, Charlette Lydia, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.114.00003 (Box 114)
  - Brauner, Andrea G., 1963 -- 2000; UA032.002.114.00004 (Box 114)
  - Breed, Tara, 2002 -- 2004; UA032.002.114.00005 (Box 114)
  - Breckken, Jo Dell (Eickhof), 1969 -- 1973; UA032.002.114.00006 (Box 114)
  - Brennan, Karen Sue, 1985 -- 1987; UA032.002.114.00007 (Box 114)
  - Brennan, Karen M., 1985 -- 1987; UA032.002.114.00008 (Box 114)
  - Brenner, Brett, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.114.00009 (Box 114)
  - Brenner, Cynthia, 1975 -- 1977; UA032.002.114.00010 (Box 114)
  - Brescia, Nancy Ann (Mayeda), 1979 -- 1983; UA032.002.114.00011 (Box 114)
  - Brelau, Janet Emily, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.114.00012 (Box 114)
  - Bretton, Pamela, 1978 -- 1980; UA032.002.114.00013 (Box 114)
  - Bretz, Jonathan Carl, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.114.00014 (Box 114)
  - Brewster, Deborah J., 1983 -- 1987; UA032.002.114.00015 (Box 114)
  - Brezinsky, Sarah, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.114.00016 (Box 114)
  - Bridges, Kristen, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.114.00017 (Box 114)
  - Brienza, Deborah A., 1984 -- 1988; UA032.002.114.00018 (Box 114)
  - Brighton, Christine P., 1988 -- 1990; UA032.002.114.00019 (Box 114)
  - Britton, Patricia, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.114.00020 (Box 114)
  - Brochu, Jamie, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.114.00021 (Box 114)
  - Brod, Abbey, 1981 -- 1982; UA032.002.114.00022 (Box 114)
  - Brader, Cindy, 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.114.00023 (Box 114)
  - Brody, Mrs. Stephen J. (Kochman, Irene), 1958 -- 1960; UA032.002.114.00024 (Box 114)
  - Brody, Patti Robin, 1971 -- 1991; UA032.002.114.00025 (Box 114)
  - Brogdon, Kelly, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.114.00026 (Box 114)
  - Brooks, Audrey I., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.114.00027 (Box 114)
  - Brooks, Kimberly, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.114.00028 (Box 114)
  - Brossman, Lisa Marie, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.114.00029 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Bette Lou, 1963; UA032.002.114.00030 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Evelyn, 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.114.00031 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Mrs. Howard (Sanni, Joanne), 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.114.00032 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Lois Ann, 1960; UA032.002.114.00033 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Sara Ann Hargreaves, 1979 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00034 (Box 114)
  - Brown, Stephanie L., 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.114.00035 (Box 114)
  - Brukilacchio, Lisa, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.114.00036 (Box 114)
  - Brumer, Deborah, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.114.00037 (Box 114)
  - Bryant, Anne Dagata, 1971 -- 1976; UA032.002.114.00038 (Box 114)
  - Buckley, Patricia, 1991 -- 1994; UA032.002.114.00039 (Box 114)
  - Buckley, Victoria, 1978 -- 1980; UA032.002.114.00040 (Box 114)
  - Budar, Mrs. Gilman P., 1956 -- 1960; UA032.002.114.00041 (Box 114)
  - Bugden, Mark, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.114.00042 (Box 114)
  - Buki, Susan, 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.114.00043 (Box 114)
  - Bullock, Ann, 1963 -- 1967; UA032.002.114.00044 (Box 114)
  - Bumpus, Mary Cathleen, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.114.00045 (Box 114)
  - Bumsted, Mrs. John M. (Wood, Patience), 1958 -- 1993; UA032.002.114.00046 (Box 114)
  - Burd, Celia, 1999 -- 2002; UA032.002.114.00047 (Box 114)
  - Burden, Betsy-MacLeod, 1961 -- 1963; UA032.002.114.00048 (Box 114)
  - Burg, Julie, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.114.00049 (Box 114)
  - Burger, Allison Grace, 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.114.00050 (Box 114)
  - Burgin, Mrs. Lewis (Stanton, Muriel E.), 1962 -- 1967; UA032.002.114.00051 (Box 114)
  - Burke, Cheryl Ann, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.114.00052 (Box 114)
  - Burke, Julie, 2006; UA032.002.114.00053 (Box 114)
  - Burnham, Susan James (Giguere), 1965 -- 1966; UA032.002.114.00054 (Box 114)
  - Burrowes, Susan M., 1998 -- 2001; UA032.002.114.00055 (Box 114)
  - Burton, Alice Elizabeth, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.114.00056 (Box 114)
  - Busman, Gail D., 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.114.00057 (Box 114)
  - Buxton, Jennifer, 1998 -- 2007; UA032.002.114.00058 (Box 114)
  - Bydlinski, Jayne P., 1979 -- 1984; UA032.002.114.00059 (Box 114)
  - Bye, Amelia C., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.114.00060 (Box 114)
  - Byer, Robin Beth, 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.114.00061 (Box 114)
  - Byrnes, Julie, 1988 -- 1990; UA032.002.114.00062 (Box 114)
  - Byron-Snow, Meredith, 1995 -- 1998; UA032.002.114.00063 (Box 114)
  - Cabral, Jenny, 2000 -- 2003; UA032.002.114.00064 (Box 114)
  - Caiati, Andrea B., 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.114.00065 (Box 114)
  - Caldwell, Deborah, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.114.00066 (Box 114)
  - Callaghan, Kathleen, 2004 -- 2008; UA032.002.114.00067 (Box 114)
  - Callahan, Stephen, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.114.00068 (Box 114)
  - Camann, Carolyn, 1978 -- 1982; UA032.002.114.00069 (Box 114)
  - Camelio, Andria, 2003 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00070 (Box 114)
  - Cameron, Lisen Burgess, 1975 -- 1978; UA032.002.114.00071 (Box 114)
  - Campbell, Constance Louise, 1959 -- 1963; UA032.002.114.00072 (Box 114)
  - Campbell, Elizabeth T., 1981 -- 1986; UA032.002.114.00073 (Box 114)
  - Canavan, Mary L., 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.114.00074 (Box 114)
  - Cantalupa, Marie, 1989 -- 1992; UA032.002.114.00075 (Box 114)
  - Canter, Abigail, 2002 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00076 (Box 114)
  - Cantor, Sue (Gershen), 1962 -- 1965; UA032.002.114.00077 (Box 114)
  - Capanna, Phyllis M., 1975 -- 1987; UA032.002.114.00078 (Box 114)
  - Cappello, Donna M., 1987; UA032.002.114.00079 (Box 114)
  - Caravati, Elaine Virginia, 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.114.00080 (Box 114)
  - Carboneau, Joan, 1977 -- 1985; UA032.002.114.00081 (Box 114)
  - Carbonneau, Marie, 1989 -- 1995; UA032.002.114.00082 (Box 114)
  - Carda, Katherine, 2004 -- 2007; UA032.002.114.00083 (Box 114)
  - Carew, Mary E., 1986 -- 1989; UA032.002.114.00084 (Box 114)
  - Carey, Marie Kathleen, 1984 -- 1991; UA032.002.114.00085 (Box 114)
  - Carey, Marie, 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.114.00086 (Box 114)
  - Carlin, Lisa McGovern, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.114.00087 (Box 114)
  - Carman, Carrie, 2005 -- 2007; UA032.002.114.00088 (Box 114)
  - Caron, Susan, 1995 -- 1999; UA032.002.114.00089 (Box 114)
  - Carrabes, Karen Marie, 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.114.00090 (Box 114)
  - Carriker, Linda, 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.114.00091 (Box 114)
  - Carriker, Neal Armstrong, 1975 -- 1977; UA032.002.114.00092 (Box 114)
  - Carroll, Margaret, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.114.00093 (Box 114)
  - Carson, Christine, 1991 -- 1995; UA032.002.114.00094 (Box 114)
  - Carson, Stacey J., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.114.00095 (Box 114)
  - Caruso, Deborah, 2002 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00096 (Box 114)
  - Carvalho, Wendy Jill, 1984 -- 1986; UA032.002.114.00097 (Box 114)
  - Carver, Cathy M., 1986 -- 1990; UA032.002.114.00098 (Box 114)
  - Carver, Cynthia O. (Oakes), 1979 -- 1983; UA032.002.114.00099 (Box 114)
  - Casey, Caroline, 2002; UA032.002.114.00100 (Box 114)
  - Casey, Michelle, 2000 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00101 (Box 114)
  - Cashion, Amy, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.114.00102 (Box 114)
  - Casser, Roni, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.114.00103 (Box 114)
  - Cassidy, Donna, 1991 -- 1992; UA032.002.114.00104 (Box 114)
  - Cassidy, Jill, 1987 -- 1989; UA032.002.114.00105 (Box 114)
  - Cassidy-Fritz, Karen P., 1986 -- 1990; UA032.002.114.00106 (Box 114)
  - Castrinakis, Alexandra, 2001 -- 2005; UA032.002.114.00107 (Box 114)
  - Cataldo, Cristinia, 1992 -- 1999; UA032.002.114.00108 (Box 114)
  - Cataldo, Christine, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00001 (Box 115)
  - Cataldo, Jean, 2002 -- 2008; UA032.002.115.00002 (Box 115)
  - Catizone, Kristina, 1993 -- 1996; UA032.002.115.00003 (Box 115)
  - Cawley, Jane, 1996 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00004 (Box 115)
  - Cayetano, Linda (Manchester), 1961 -- 1965; UA032.002.115.00005 (Box 115)
  - Cernak, Jennifer, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.115.00006 (Box 115)
  - Ceurvels, Susan, 1987 -- 1990; UA032.002.115.00007 (Box 115)
  - Chabot, Laurie A., 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.115.00008 (Box 115)
  - Chan, Anna, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.115.00009 (Box 115)
  - Chan, Lung, 1997 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00010 (Box 115)
  - Chandler, Robin L., 1979 -- 1983; UA032.002.115.00011 (Box 115)
  - Chandley, Nancy E., 1975 -- 1976; UA032.002.115.00012 (Box 115)
  - Chandra, Divya, 1988 -- 1989; UA032.002.115.00013 (Box 115)
  - Chang, Cho-Chin, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.115.00014 (Box 115)
  - Chea, Mary, 1989 -- 1990; UA032.002.115.00015 (Box 115)
  - Chee, Nancy, 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.115.00016 (Box 115)
  - Chen, Christine, 1979 -- 1994; UA032.002.115.00017 (Box 115)
  - Chen, Martha, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00018 (Box 115)
  - Cheng, Fawn, 2002 -- 2006; UA032.002.115.00019 (Box 115)
  - Chentow, Ruth E. (Sweedler), 1966 -- 1967; UA032.002.115.00020 (Box 115)
  - Chimbel, Jody Sue, 1975 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00021 (Box 115)
  - Chin, Helen N., 1986; UA032.002.115.00022 (Box 115)
  - Chin, Sally Y., 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.115.00023 (Box 115)
  - Chivers, Kristine (Calney), 1969 -- 1972; UA032.002.115.00024 (Box 115)
  - Chobanian, Lori, 1991 -- 1995; UA032.002.115.00025 (Box 115)
  - Christmann, Elizabeth A., 1984 -- 1988; UA032.002.115.00026 (Box 115)
  - Christopher, Ronald, 1998 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00027 (Box 115)
  - Chung, Judy J., 2001 -- 2005; UA032.002.115.00028 (Box 115)
  - Church, Mary Anne, 1972 -- 1983; UA032.002.115.00029 (Box 115)
  - Ciferni, Claudia, 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.115.00030 (Box 115)
  - Ciszewki, Leslee Ann (Fortin), 1967 -- 1972; UA032.002.115.00031 (Box 115)
  - Clark, Grace Alice (Williams), 1964 -- 1967; UA032.002.115.00032 (Box 115)
  - Clark, Jennifer, 2001 -- 2004; UA032.002.115.00033 (Box 115)
  - Clark, Robin Fiske, 1975 -- 1976; UA032.002.115.00034 (Box 115)
  - Clarke, Karen, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.115.00035 (Box 115)
  - Clemson, Christine, 1982 -- 1994; UA032.002.115.00036 (Box 115)
  - Cleveland, Mareen P., 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.115.00037 (Box 115)
  - Clinton, Mary, 1992 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00038 (Box 115)
  - Coates, Annette, 1970 -- 1974; UA032.002.115.00039 (Box 115)
  - Cobern, Amy, 2000 -- 2004; UA032.002.115.00040 (Box 115)
  - Cody, Melissa, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.115.00041 (Box 115)
  - Cofer, Patricia, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.115.00042 (Box 115)
  - Cogan, Beverly S., 1963 -- 1967; UA032.002.115.00043 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Deborah Susan, 1965 -- 1969; UA032.002.115.00044 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Ellie, 1985 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00045 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Helen Sue, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.115.00046 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Irma Roslyn (Aronson), 1945 -- 1949; UA032.002.115.00047 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Linda Beth, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.115.00048 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Ricki Lynn, 1976 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00049 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Risa, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.115.00050 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Sandra Susan, 1975 -- 1978; UA032.002.115.00051 (Box 115)
  - Cohen, Terri Ann (Feldman), 1965 -- 1969; UA032.002.115.00052 (Box 115)
  - Colclough, Laura, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.115.00053 (Box 115)
  - Cole, Paula Aline, 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.115.00054 (Box 115)
  - Colley, Anne, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.115.00055 (Box 115)
  - Collins, Rebecca, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00056 (Box 115)
  - Colman, Wendy Ann, 1968 -- 1972; UA032.002.115.00057 (Box 115)
  - Comeau, Ellen, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.115.00058 (Box 115)
  - Comenzo, Julie (Theise), 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.115.00059 (Box 115)
  - Commaroto, Linda Susanne (Pounds), 1967 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00060 (Box 115)
  - Condit, Clare Gage, 1966 -- 1968; UA032.002.115.00061 (Box 115)
  - Conneely, Kathy (Sheehy), 1995 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00062 (Box 115)
  - Connelly, Thomas, 1996 -- 1997; UA032.002.115.00063 (Box 115)
  - Conrad, Carlyle (Claypool), 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.115.00064 (Box 115)
  - Cook, Dana, 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.115.00065 (Box 115)
  - Cook, Pamela Douglas, 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.115.00066 (Box 115)
  - Cooney, Theresa, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.115.00067 (Box 115)
  - Cooper, Catherine, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.115.00068 (Box 115)
  - Cooper, Leslie Marlene, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.115.00069 (Box 115)
  - Cooper, Suzanne, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.115.00070 (Box 115)
  - Cooperman, Sue Anne, 1977 -- 1979; UA032.002.115.00071 (Box 115)
  - Coplan, Neil, 1991 -- 1994; UA032.002.115.00072 (Box 115)
  - Coppelman, Marcy, 1975 -- 1991; UA032.002.115.00073 (Box 115)
  - Corcoran, Jeanne, 2004 -- 2005; UA032.002.115.00074 (Box 115)
  - Corcoran, Kathleen, 2003 -- 2007; UA032.002.115.00075 (Box 115)
  - Corno, Megin, 2000 -- 2007; UA032.002.115.00076 (Box 115)
  - Corrigan, Stephanie, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.115.00077 (Box 115)
  - Costa, Ursula, 1998 -- 1999; UA032.002.115.00078 (Box 115)
  - Cote, Rebekah H., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.115.00079 (Box 115)
  - Cotton, Lauren Amy, 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.115.00080 (Box 115)
  - Coughlin, Kathleen, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.115.00081 (Box 115)
  - Courtney, Elizabeth, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.115.00082 (Box 115)
  - Courtsunis, Demetra G., 1970 -- 1973; UA032.002.115.00083 (Box 115)
  - Cousineau, Shari, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.115.00084 (Box 115)